I totally feel this mask tingling.
It smells good, it feels good, this is a winner.
I really believe J Lo knows exactly what she's talking about.
This is a winner.
Now, let's talk about taking masks off.
What you want to do, you'll want to be extremely careful when you're taking a mask off.
Whether it's like this, or it comes off with water, or a peel off one.
My best friend loves peel off ones, she's like peeling stuff off all day, I don't know, she loves that.
But whatever you're doing you want to be careful when you're taking off the mask because you don't want to irritate your skin.
Where, normally, I would take my hands and just rinse.
This is when I actually do use a wash cloth to take off.
Immerse it.
And, again, you can use either cold water, some people like to use cold water in the morning because it gives them kind of a pick me up.
I like to do my mask in the evening time so I like warm water.
Never hot water, but warm water because it kind of gives me that comforting feel.
But, it's up to you to what you like.
Take your wash cloth, gently remove, circular motions.
Circular motions, remember gentle because the wash cloth itself is a natural exfoliant for skin so it's going to help also with the mask.
Gentle, circular sweeping motions to take the mask off.
Wow!
That feels amazing.
Okay.
I might have to send J Lo an extra baby gift because she has totally turned me on to the right things.
Okay, so the twins are going to get something extra for this.
This is good.
Oh, my.
Oh.
I'm feeling very saucy and Latino right now, I am.
Okay.
And, that's how you take off the mask.